Elias H. Dagher Apt. 3308A 121 Campus Drive Lyman Residences Stanford, California 94305

October 14, 1999

#### Dear Recruiter:

I have a sincere interest in electrical engineering, and specifically in computer hardware, digital, analog, and mixed signal design. I have a strong educational background supported by several engineering internships.

During my undergraduate schooling, I designed and fabricated a digital floating-point multiplier chip. From that experience with chip design, I chose for my senior design project an integrated switched capacitor digital to analog converter which is heavily centered around the design of an analog operational amplifier. During my graduate schooling, I focused my studies on computer hardware design. I added breadth to my studies by taking courses in analog design, computer systems, and communications.

In addition, I spent two summers working for Rockwell Semiconductor Systems as an intern. During those internships, I was exposed to advanced commercial design tools, such as, HSPICE, Verilog, Synopsis, and Chrysalis. During my second internship, I participated in the hardware implementation of a digital communications chip set and worked with a team of analog and digital engineers.

I urge you to review my résumé. Should my background and credentials suit your needs please call me at (650) 497-2624 or email me at dagher@stanford.edu.

Sincerely,

Elias H. Dagher

Enclosure

# **ELIAS HANI DAGHER**

Apt. 3308A • 121 Campus Drive • Lyman Residences • Stanford, California 94305

(650) 497-2624 or (702)228-8049 October 14, 1999

Email: dagher@stanford.edu

#### **OBJECTIVE**

A challenging position in Computer Hardware Design.

## **EDUCATION**

MASTER OF SCIENCE ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING GRADUATION: DEC. 1999
Stanford University Stanford, California

GPA: 3.755/4.0

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING

SUMMA CUM LAUDE

University of Nevada, Las Vegas

GRADUATED: DEC. 1998

Las Vegas, Nevada

GPA: 4.0/4.0

HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATE

VALEDICTORIAN

Cimarron-Memorial High School

Graduated: June 1994

Las Vegas, Nevada

GPA: 4.7/4.0

Las Vegas, NV

#### **EXPERIENCE**

LAB ASSISTANT

MARCH 1996-DECEMBER 1998

**NEVADA CENTER FOR ADVANCED** 

COMPUTATIONAL METHODS

Programmed in Borland's Object Windows Library to develop several MS Windows applications dealing with fluid dynamics.

SUMMER INTERN

MAY 1998-AUGUST 1998

**ROCKWELL SEMICONDUCTOR SYSTEMS** - *Network Access* San Diego, CA Assisted in the digital hardware implementation of system level designs using Verilog. Verified Verilog code functionality. Developed file manipulation scripts in Perl.

SUMMER INTERN

MAY 1997-AUGUST 1997

**ROCKWELL SEMICONDUCTOR SYSTEMS - CAD** 

San Diego, CA

Tested, evaluated, and compared Avant's HSPICE and Mentor Graphics' Accusim circuit simulators. Performed metastability analysis and cell library characterization.

LAB ASSISTANT

**SUMMER 1995** 

DEPARTMENT OF ENERGY-EPSCOR YOUNG SCHOLAR

Las Vegas, NV

Participated in the numerical modeling of an electro-static air filter for the Department of Energy.

#### **COURSES**

Advanced Computer Organization, Processor Design, Computer Architecture and Organization, VLSI Design, Logic Synthesis of VLSI Circuits, Computer-Aided System Design, Circuits, Logic Design, Electronics, Signals and Systems, Analog Integrated Circuits Design, Electromagnetics, Feedback and Controls, Digital System Design, Digital Electronics, Statistical Signal Processing, Digital Filtering, Design of Information Appliances, Power, Technical Writing, Numerical Analysis, Operating Systems, Compilers, Computer Networking, C Programming, FORTRAN Programming, and Assembly Programming.

## SKILLS

- Designed and fabricated an integrated switched capacitor DAC for Senior Design project.
- C Designed and fabricated an integrated floating point parallel multiplier for VLSI Design class project.
- C Designed Verilog model of an interconnection network router for Advanced Computer Organization class.
- C Designed electromagnetic catapult for Electromagnetics class project.
- C Operating Systems: Unix, X Windows, and MS Windows
- CAD Tools: SPICE, IRSIM, MAGIC, HSPICE, Accusim
- C Programming Languages: Verilog, C, C++, FORTRAN, Assembly, Perl

### HONORS AND ACTIVITIES

- 1997 Barry M. Goldwater Scholar One out of 282 recipients in a national competition of 1,164 university students.
- C U.N.L.V. Dean's Honor list 1994-1998
- C U.N.L.V. Honors College
- C Scholarships: *Elaine Wynn Valedictorian*, *Harold and Mayme Stocker*, Mary Doughtery/Standly H. Kaplan, Mary Doughtery Honors Program, Old Crows Society, and Mitzi Hughes Alumni
- C IEEE Member 1996-1999

#### REFERENCES

Available upon request.